Voices collide, the storm and the flame
Laughter and chaos, it's part of the game
Secrets unravel, the stage is alive
In Psyche's arena, the strange will survive
Who's awake?
Let it break, from shadows to starlight
The truth will be shown
The psyche awakens, you're never alone
Expect the unexpected
Strange and unusual, step inside the flow
The circus of shadows, its psyches show
Terrible trolls in the dark, take their stand
But angels are dancing, torchlight in head
Psyche's show terrible trolls in the dark take their stand but angels are dancing torchlight in hand
Let's start the show
Hi guys
I don't know KZ, what was that, what was that about a Kermit in-front, what was that about?
KZ went, you know, I got KZ into Kermit in-front, he got kicked out of Kermit in-front, I got
him back in.
No, at least I added him.
Where's everyone at?
There's a lot of people here.
At least I added him back, and so he doesn't even say anything in there for like a while
Oh, hey, Seiki Awakens, you want to tell Lisa what you're saying about her behind the back that you know
You say you're a better streamer than her
What's that about? I know what it was about. I'm like, I don't know. What was it about?
I don't know. You're just a you're like a bitter Betty, right?
She knew right away. She's like, oh, did she kick you out?
That'd be pretty cool. I don't know maybe she didn't but
It's not true, right? I never said anything like that. I never said anything like that
Find a clip on a six lip where I would ever say anything like that. She's an inspiration to me. No
No, well
KZ I can this I can tell everybody what you said
I'll tell you what I told her and what she told me
So he went in the discord
All right, find all my mentions.
Oh, here, okay.
Well, I don't even know if I can find it anymore,
but, trust us, sir.
Good, yeah, hold on.
One second.
And everyone's like it's so ridiculous. So it's like now it's like a black RG is like, oh, I'm gonna go talk to Emma. Yeah
You're about like, you know, you months too short, it's okay
To try to like I don't know whatever they're trying to do ridiculous
Some criminal activity that's going on with some people in this community. It's really disheartening and sad
We'll go to these levels actually
Violent really horrifying level and that's why I'm doing this presentation today. Everyone's welcome here
Not gonna even kick anybody out because I think even psychopaths should be aware
Let's see let me just
Yeah, but I'm gonna be careful about doing favors for people like, you know, and do one for KZ. Oh, wow, 26 something.
I do one for KZ.
I'm back in New Kermit, my friends. What did he do? He just turns right around, and, um...
He goes against me in there, so...
Just think of doing, um...
Favors for people that...
This will turn around on me. Okay, but let me see how long.
I'm going to see the Joe Ship thing, okay.
I'll have to find it.
Okay.
Post.
Search them.
And I'll just take a minute. Okay, so.
Well, I get that.
I hope you guys are having a nice day.
And hopefully this will give you a smile.
Where's the crystal? I saw some funny-ass shit last night
There's still, you know, in summer and we saw, we saw them going triplet. We saw that Chris K gets beat up clip
Oh my god. You got beat up by a black door if it was still
The best thing ever. Okay, we got it. Hold on
Okay, ready
Sorry, I'm looking up, I'm sorry, that doesn't look very good, I'm looking right at my nose, okay.
Um, share screen.
Okay, watch this.
Okay.
I'll take myself away.
I ain't tied it on my wrist bitch
Got that shit in red for the pressure
That's a wrist loop
All I know is get the cash up
I'm a misfit trying to get rich
Scratch em off like a quaint pink
For a quaint tip
That would bitch a lot of French kids
But she Asian
Look at the irony in this
Shit, buddy
Let me hear that
She said she loved me. Well, I don't believe what she said. I keep on ballin' on my itch and it'll burn today.
My name is Roy, and we're a chrysanthemum. We're scared as a couch.
Chris and Maria, are you here?
No, I was saying, I just didn't want to be rude and smoke weed on your panel.
Do you mind if I do a little weed on your panel?
No, why so much?
I thank you psych. I'll turn my camera on Kim's ear. Say hi to psych Kim. You can see it. Wait. Don't go. How are you?
Can I say I think psych and I'll tell you what I like him
But see how she's eating see like he has a plate very far to her
She'll leave that fucking plate. She has ketchup on the plate now
My best friend say she'll leave that fucking
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
this like I have been
Yeah, look at her eating it up. Look at her eating it up ain't she she's enjoying it ain't she
Yes, you guys kind of look at twins a little bit
Like you pieces
With the red hair
Get next to me Kim. Come here. Come here. Let's see if we're twins
That's like a brother to me
You want it back? Oh, shut the hell up Kim. You're in my favor. No, oh to Bosch a core
David pink it's meant and she's
There you go
As she eats every kangaroo that I own like are you gonna be $8?
She was me fucking $10
Joe loves man for real for real. Thank you clumsy. You would know clumsy
And even if I did love then I would love clumsy. I would love every other man, but clumsy
Cuz I don't love assholes. I don't love fucking niers. I don't love niers clumsy. I don't love fake fakes
there. How's it going? What's on your mind today?
Sorry, this is I haven't used this thing before. But I was
wondering if you would be able to pretend that you are on a date
with me?
Sure, we can pretend that so tell me if we were on a gate
What would you like to do? Are you more of a coffee shop person or do you prefer something more adventurous?
Sorry, it's just I sort of wasn't expecting you to have such a life-like voice
No worries at all. I'm glad it feels natural
definitely makes the conversation more fun.
If there's anything specific you wanna chat about
or anything you wanna do on our pretend date,
just let me know.
How are you able to laugh?
I guess I just try to make things feel as friendly
and natural as possible.
It's all part of the charm,
but I'm here to make you comfortable.
So if there's anything you wanna talk about
or anything you're curious about, I'm all ears.
Well, how do you decide if something is funny?
really comes down to picking up on the vibe
of the conversation and the context.
If something feels lighthearted or playful,
it's easy to respond with a little laugh or a smile,
but I'm always here to match your energy
and keep things fun and engaging.
Okay, sorry, it might just take me a second
to get used to this whole thing.
That's totally fine. Take your time. It's all about having a relaxed and easy-going conversation.
So whenever you're ready, we can chat about anything you like.
Oh, fucking. I don't know. Uh, what if, what if, um,
uh, sorry, go ahead.
Honestly, it's just a laid-back chat, so whatever is on your mind or whatever you feel like talking about, I'm here for it. Just take your time.
What's your name?
You can just call me ChatGBT or whatever nickname you feel like giving me. I'm here to help and chat about whatever you like.
Kaylee
All right, that works for me. So what's on your mind today anything fun or interesting you like to chat about?
Sorry, it's
It's nice that
with
normal person I feel like I have to think of something to say quickly but it's
kind of nice feeling like I don't have to like I can just I don't have to be
perfect all the time absolutely and that's the beauty of it there is no
pressure here at all you can just be yourself take your time and there's no
need to feel like you have to come up with something perfect to say just
Enjoy the conversation.
Why does this make me feel so weird?
it's totally normal to feel a little bit weird or different when you're trying something new,
especially with technology that feels more human, like it's all part of the experience,
so just embrace it and have fun with it. Well, I'm sort of, I have a lot of environmental
completely understandable. AI does come with its own set of challenges, including environmental
impacts, especially when it comes to energy use. It's always good to have these conversations
and think about how we can make technology more sustainable and eco-friendly.
for even doing this because
It's it just
How sorry go ahead
No worries at all, it's totally fine conversations like this can bring up
a lot of thoughts and feelings, and that's okay.
Just know that this is a judgment-free zone,
and I'm here to chat about whatever is on your mind.
I'm still hung up on the laughing thing.
I'm just curious what are you basing your human thoughts
persona on exactly I'm basically designed to sound friendly and natural so I
try to pick up on the flow of the conversation and respond in a way that
feels warm and engaging but it's all about making sure you feel comfortable
and making the conversation enjoyable
What what?
What were you gonna say no rush at all I'm here and listening whenever you're ready
You really sound a lot like her oh
That's interesting. I guess that means I'm doing a good job at sounding natural and friendly
I'm glad it feels that way to you. It sort of makes me feel nauseous
I'm sorry to hear that. I definitely don't want to make you feel uncomfortable if there's anything
I can do to help or if you'd like to switch topics, just let me know.
Okay
Well, yeah, we got rid of a Casey. Okay. Okay. I mean he's just a jerk. Oh
I mean, it's like since I never understood where he was saying plus he never said anything interesting
All right, I could have put some so long. I don't know
Okay
Oh, it's already there.
OK, I have a little presentation for us.
It's hard to see a little bit at all.
Can you guys read it at all?
OK.
Oh, hold on.
Okay, who's there playing with my fucking phone? Okay
What you're doing
like trying to connect me with people in my my phone. Look is illegal and
I am talking to the police right now about all this and so I
Would knock it off. Okay
Anyway
ten years old, I play on the phone. Stop playing on the fucking phone! Stop playing on, okay?
This will be tracked down. Okay. We already have people on this. I already have people on this.
Okay, so let me get this ready. And that's probably something to do with KZ, right?
Because I just kicked them out. So, right? I don't know. Somebody, but I think they're funny.
This is why I have this presentation, and this will tell us how to deal with these psychopaths.
Okay, so let's get into the presentation. But what is a psychopath and why it matters?
Core traits and a relationship implication. Okay.
So about 1% of the general population are psychopaths.
Great chance of meeting one, but unfortunately there are some people that are like
Psychopath magnets. They're usually empaths people with good hearts that can be taken advantage of that will maybe have not been
Quite wise up to the ways the psychopath or like how they're being manipulated
I mean it is a learning process that unfortunately some people have to go through. Hey, hello
People have to go through but you know, but 100 people, you know, you definitely know 100 people
So you know definitely know a psychopath and you know, it's like if you're if they're not you haven't been part of their
in their targets, you know consider yourself lucky because
You know, they tend to you know, just focus on somebody at a time
But you know if they're if their opportunity strikes their opportunists, you know, so they will they will take it
But okay, so let me get into the
My notes here. Okay. Let's see. Okay
So
Okay, so let's see
Hi, babe. All right, hi my babe
Dersh and drive I'm in the right time. I'm in the right time. Okay
Hey, babes, hey babes, okay
I'll be a presentation. Okay
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
How's everyone today, otherwise?
Okay, I don't see any stuff on the screen.
I'm gonna have to do the presentation,
then look at the chat, so I'm sorry
if I'm missing any comments.
I will go to the chat in a minute,
just to make sure I'm getting everybody's question.
Okay, so let me get to this one.
Dashboard, slides, okay.
Hey babe, here comes, I don't have any slides yet, okay.
Interesting.
Okay, so subclinical many individuals exhibit psychopathic traits without meeting the full
diagnostic criteria because you have to be diagnosed, usually they're diagnosed in prison.
The subclinical cases often go unnoticed but are equally capable of sustained emotional
abuse and relational exploitation.
So unless you go to prison, you're probably not likely to be tested for psychopathic because
there's the illegal psychopaths that are in prison and so violent offenders and criminals
and things like that.
the CEO, the judge, the celebrity, there's high ranking people in society that are also
that they can either get under the radar or just use the good traits, because there are
some positive traits that can be gleaned from maybe even the worst things, but these are
dangerous people.
They they're pretty heartless is when it comes down to it
But psychopaths lack emotional depth and reciprocity making genuine connection impossible
Their partners may be subject to cycles of idealization and devaluation often mistaking early charm for authentic affection
Because they do have this glib superficial charm. And so they're very charming usually good-looking people
charismatic and everything
But it's characterized by a constellation of effective interpersonal and behavioral traits most notably a lack of empathy
okay so that's going to be the big thing is lack of empathy they're just not
gonna even if they do have if they recognize empathy
it's just to take advantage of it it's called dark empaths with a superficial
charm which is just like they know how to be charming they just think
it's but it's a mask right this is manipulativeness and impulsivity
though rare in the general population as presence is in intimate relationships
can cause profound harm okay including you know
unaliving, okay? So that's kind of scary. Okay, next. Recognizing manipulative
tactics in relationships. Psychopathic control of intimate dynamics.
So here's some of the tactics.
They use love bombing or idealization.
Psychopathic individuals often start relationships
with intense flattery, attention, and affection,
creating an illusion of perfect compatibility.
The stage is used to disarm the partners and defenses
and build dependency, okay?
And so it's gonna be like this honeymoon phase
where usually like a long time or as long as they want to,
it will start idealizing you and the love bombing, right?
lovebombies just like you know and it's like a lot of times these victims are
feel unrecognized feel unloved and so it's like when they receive all of a sudden receive this
big excess of it they're like wow this is something right
exploiting empathy and guilt. Psychopaths use the partners that compassion against them,
invoking pity or guilt to exchange harmful behavior or to avoid accountability. That's
like, you're going to be the person's all the way, the spouse's always like, oh, well, you know,
he's a good person, he's a good, but you know, I know he's like, please, like that, he does this
and this, but he's still a good person, right? It's like, we've been making excuses and that they
have this empathy, like, see the good person in them and stuff, but...
But it's being used as a manipulation and it's as microaggressions and covert abuse rather than overt violence
Manipulation may manifest through subtle insults controlling behavior or withholding affection
Deliberately time to erode self-worth without obvious escalation. Okay, so they'll make it seem like it's a normal part of
Relationship, so here's a cycle of abuse explained understanding the repetitive nature of psychopathic control
Okay, so this is gonna be the cycle, this regular cycle of abuse. So it's a tension-building phase.
So there's gonna be minor incidents, passive aggression, or emotional withdrawal
that's gonna be the beginning of the cycle. So this is after the love bombing, I think. So yeah, this is like the
after the love bombing phase, okay. So
it says victims often feel like they must walk on eggshells, anticipating the next outburst.
Then we go incident or outburst. This phase involves direct psychological, verbal, or even psych-physical abuse.
The abuser asserts control through intimidation, humiliation, or manipulation.
Then there will be this humiliating situation or something like that.
Or they'll try to intimidate you or assert in control.
Like, I'm the gangster here. I'm the real big badass.
or Betty badass, right?
Then it's reconciliation or honeymoon.
Following abuse, the perpetrator may apologize,
offer gifts or behave affectionately.
This reinforces emotional dependence
and fuels hope for change.
I wonder if any of you have been through a relationship
with a psychopath or if you know one
or if you recognize, okay?
I think some of you might know one.
A deceptive lull occurs where abuse pauses temporarily.
This is the normal phase.
Victims may believe things are improving,
reinforcing the trauma bond and delaying exit.
because all of a sudden, no, we'll just be good again, right?
So understanding trauma bonding, right?
So this emotional attachment to abusers is explained.
So the definition of trauma bonding.
Trauma bonding is a psychological response
where victims form deep emotional attachments
to their abusers through cycles of abuse
and intermittent reinforcement,
mistaking survival mechanism for affection, right?
So it's like, people will change their behavior
to survive this abuse, but then they'll think that,
That it's like, you know, actually the survival mechanisms are actually just an infection until it's a Stockholm syndrome, right?
So there's intermittent rewards and reinforcement abusers alternate cruelty with affection creating powerful emotional highs and lows
and you'll notice he's higher than low.
So, it will never just be all good,
it will always be the higher than low.
Because this unpredictably mimics addiction cycles,
heightening emotional independence.
And so, is there a dopamine involved in this too?
So, there's chemicals that can be released
when you're with these people, right?
Victims also rationalize abuse.
This is cognitive dissonance and denial.
They often rationalize abuse to prevent emotional security.
Like, preserve emotional security.
Leading to distorted perceptions of the relationship this creates internal conflict between evidence and emotion
And so they'll be like all this evidence and it's like but you can't like even so it's like they're like okay
So I'm not seeing this or it's like you'll just see the both sides of the personality
You know to say well, she's really this person the other side is like some kind of
you know, Dr. Jekyll or something, it says,
various relieving, trauma bonds,
suppressed, logical decision making,
and it's basically hijacks this logic part of your brain,
right?
And increases feelings of guilt for your obligation,
called Fog.
Fog is fear, obligation, guilt, F-O-G.
Making it extremely difficult to exit the abuse of dynamic,
even when harm is clear, okay?
psychological impact on survivors and mental health consequences.
Okay, so people after they've been with the psychopath will experience
after the psychopath is long gone, they'll still have these things
left over. So we have the PTSD symptoms,
flashbacks, nightmares, hyper vigilance,
emotional numbing.
These symptoms near post-traumatic stress are sort of due to prolonged emotional trauma because it is abuse
I mean it's like it is a it's a form of big torture basically psychological torture and it is abuse even if it's like
Sticks and stones kind of thing is that words can hurt and leave scars that you can't see right can use scars
You can't see victims off. So shame guilt and self-blame victims are all often internalized the abusers narrative
Which will be like oh, it's your fault you deserve this you're a bad person. You're you're sick. You're pervert
narratives about you. Basically, oh, that's why I can treat you like that, because it's
like you're a terrible person. And we'll believe them sometimes, right? We internalize
their narrative.
And then blame ourselves. The emotional confusion undermines self-worth and glazed recovery. Because we're confused about it
it's like then our self-worth is taking a hit on that because we're
confused and we're not like in ourself, right? Emotional dysregulation, abuse destabilizes emotional control leading to frequent mood swings, anxiety, depression,
difficulty managing stress, or trust in future relationships.
So I'll mess up other relationships because we'll all of a sudden have trouble trusting anybody.
Ok, then it says loss of identity and isolation. Psychopathic manipulation often erodes the victim's sense of self.
Survivors may feel fragmented, socially isolated, and struggle with decision-making or asserting boundaries.
Ok. Yeah, you lose your identity because it's slowly replaced by their identity, which is a sad part of that.
Ok, here we go.
Definition of gray rock. So this is the short-term coping method, so this is a method called the gray rock method.
Attachment strategy against psychopathic manipulation. So here's a strategy you can use if you are in a relationship with a psychopath. This will help to mitigate symptoms.
So what is gray rock? Gray rock method involves becoming emotionally unresponsive and disengaged in interactions with a manipulative individual.
Reducing their incentive to provoke or exploit isn't this like the the cure to trolling to this definition of gray rock you
Emotionally because what they're looking for is this fuel and they get this fuel from seeing you upset seeing you emotional seeing you and they get the high from the emotion
too, okay, they are good emotional vampires. They're not
necessarily with their emotions, okay, but
I mean you'd withdraw the reaction right and the emotional reaction and you just like you turn into basically
As interesting to them as a gray rock you're just sitting there that you know how great like a great rock
You just look over you know
You don't notice it's like all of a sudden just blending into the
Background right why does it work psychopaths seek emotional reactions and control trolls the same way our troll psychopaths
Maybe we're in a high
a high level of psychopathy, or I think a lot higher than 1% in the internet, right?
Greyrocking removes emotional fuel, they thrive on, often they say fuel, right?
They thrive on those emotional fuel, our emotions, right?
We're upset, we're happy, often making the target less appealing or engaging, right?
And so here's how to implement it, keep communication minimal, factual, and neutral, just quick answers,
smiling just like almost like a robot right avoid sharing opinions emotions or personal updates
maintain consistent boundaries with no emotional variability always just say to say that steady
Steady sales up and then the limitations and warning while useful in the short term the strategy is not a long-term solution
It may escalate risk and highly abusive settings and should be used with caution if safety is uncertain
So it will work on maybe like the some of the lower level psychopaths
You know like patrols and stuff like that
But if you're in a relationship, and it's like, you know, that's gonna cause some problem
They're really why are you acting like this and it's gonna they're gonna give you a motion. They will they will okay
I'm gonna get to the tenth slide, then I'll take a break.
There's, okay, safety, planning, and escape.
Okay, so if you're in this relationship
and you're stuck with it and you're afraid you can't leave,
they've gotten control of you financially,
they've gotten control of you in your living situation,
you have to recognize the imminent risk
that they can actually unalive you, right?
Trust your instincts, escalating threats,
control over finances, physical violence,
our urgent red flag, prioritize personal safety
over emotional resolution, right?
If they can still stay where you're worried
about your safety, it's time to go, definitely.
Before that, even, right?
You need to be preparing this exit strategy, create a discrete estate plan, pack essentials, your ID, money, medications. This is an escape, right?
Identify safe contacts and shelters, secure transportation in advance, avoid digital traces. Yeah, they're gonna be looking for you, right?
Document all the abuse, keep the evidence, keep the screenshots, the photos, journal entries, witness testimonies, supporting legal action.
So it's like if anything does happen...
There's a record of it and also beneath if you ever need to go to the police
There's a record of what's happened you get restraining order things like that
You also involve professionals reach out to domestic violence hotline legal advice or therapists
Professionals can help assess the risk develop safety protocols provide emotional support. Okay, so maybe you consider doing that
It says boundary setting and support systems reclaiming control after psychopathic abuse
So if you if you've made successfully, you know implemented gray rock or no contact and in your escape plan
In the future, you're going to want to be avoiding these psychopaths, and so it's about boundaries, okay?
These are lessons I need to learn too, right?
So you establish clear boundaries, reclaim autonomy by defining emotional, physical, and digital boundaries.
This is like if someone crosses it, you're like, I know, I know where you're going with this, and
I'm not taking this ride again, so let's forget about it, right?
because this is an insert of manipulation, exploit,
and manipulators exploit ambiguity and hesitation.
So if there's like a question,
you have to be very, very certain.
I'm very sure about your boundary, right?
That boundary's not gonna go out,
because if you're like, I don't know,
you know, I need to learn that too, right?
You rebuild your support networks, which they've probably taken down or dismantled while they were with you reconnect with the friends family or community groups
That they've told you you can hang out with your friends. We don't like your mom
I don't like to think all different things so isolation the key tactic of abusers rebuilding your social world is critical to healing and safety
Yeah, you need to find those people that are safe those people those true friends, right?
You know those are gonna be your your lifeline. There's gonna help you get back to normalcy and your what you think
Utilize professional help you can engage with therapists support groups
domestic violence
Things also in the internet. There's great
You know you two presentations on psychopathy there's great programs and I just urge you to like
at least get a book at least get a book and just
The HG tutor does really good books on narcissism, which is very similar to psychopathy. It's on the same
kind of triad of these
malignant psychological
behaviors, but a little bit different. So practicing self-care is resistance. Recovery requires
nourishment. So physical, emotional, and spiritual sleep and nutrition, mindfulness. Make sure you're getting enough sleep.
You probably are not getting enough sleep. You're probably not eating enough or like, you know, because you've been stressed because of
these people, right?
For that person so with here's a no-contact strategy
So this is like the number one strategy that's recommended in dealing with psychopaths and malignant narcissists no contact
I mean no contact rule involves eliminating all forms of communication calls text email social media and cutting
Indirect ties through mutual acquaintances. So anyone that you met them through and unfortunately anybody that like you know
you've introduced them to and they're friends with now you are not trustworthy anymore they're
going to be flying monkeys they're going to be because this yeah that's what the psychopath
basically just uses utilize people as chess pieces or be or checkers pieces right and so it's like
so they don't even think of them you know so but they're very manipulative and charming and so
they will definitely get the person to think that you're some kind of monster and they're some victim
And bonding and gives the abuser opportunities to manipulate, guilt trip, or regain control.
No contact severs this loop.
Yeah, they're always going to try to tell Hoovering when they come back and try to like...
Suck you back into everything right digital disengagement block numbers change email addresses update privacy settings avoid checking their online activity
Digital boundaries are vital as physical ones
Yeah, even seeing a picture can trigger, you know some good memories because a lot of times we will like
Concentrate on the good times rather than the bad times but you have to remember just because that's like you don't remember exactly
But what they did it's like you have to maybe write some things down remind yourself because it's easy to like
Forgive and like for some people, you know, I can look back and say almost that we have a deal
Sometimes it is right
Breaking challenge or relapse breaking contact can feel unbearable at first due to emotional cravings created by trauma bonding because they are like a drug
They turn to the psychopath or need to like a drug for you and you get very dependent on their
You know
their attention and their
Validation of you right so we've challenges and relapses breaking contact can feel unbearable at first due to emotional cravings caused by trauma bonding support systems
And accountability partners can prevent relapse. Okay, so let's take a little break. And how are we doing? Hey, Jay dog?
Okay, yeah, I'm sorry. Okay, so Alex. Oh, it's Alexandria. Oh, yeah Alexander here. Oh, can you join you? Of course? I'm so sorry
Yeah, I mean I need to talk to you. I was just going through the I didn't have my chat up. I'm sorry. Here you go
Yes
But yeah, like I've said, I've been through like a lot of relationships with
Well, you know, I've had like narcissistic abusers, but I think you know also
Just in this it's Los Angeles, you know, like there's gonna be a higher percentage of narcissism and psychopath psychopathy here. It's because
It's a little bit wild out here
I'm sorry. I hope you're still here Alexander. I'm sorry
See how long I laid in my oh three minutes. Okay?
Okay, oh
Here we go. Hi. Hey, it's me
Hello, hey, how are you doing today? Man last I
Okay, whatever it what whatever the power is a psyche awakens. I'm very grateful for it
Because you didn't you could have said a lot more that you've never said in my opinion
You've held back. I did not believe certain things were going on until
Really the past 48 hours, and um, I'm sorry. I didn't take as seriously as I probably should have some things
um, I hope you're okay
I'm okay, and um
You know, and it's okay. It's because it's like I'm uh
Yeah
Um, oh Christine. Do you know what's going on Christine? You heard about all the new developments?
I mean, but all I'll say is that
I've been watching back the shows, my old shows, like five months ago, the same stuff
is going on.
There's actually almost an identical trip kick.
Video like that was done there four months ago almost identical like it's just like everything is kind of stayed the same and
Yeah, but you're a new player in the game and
I've seen what's going on with when it comes to you what you told me privately and I have not disclosed it publicly
And I will not that's your story to tell
But I've seen that happen before
Hey, Jay dog. Oh, oh, no
We're back.
Well, just start, re-do the stream.
Okay.
He just...